<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>clusterProfiler</title>
    <link>https://guangchuangyu.github.io/clusterProfiler/</link>
    <description>Recent content on clusterProfiler</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>Released under the Artistic-2.0 license</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 06 Jun 2015 12:06:03 +0800</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://guangchuangyu.github.io/clusterProfiler/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>clusterProfiler: statistical analysis and visualization of functional profiles for genes and gene clusters</title>
      <link>https://guangchuangyu.github.io/clusterProfiler/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 06 Jun 2015 12:06:03 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://guangchuangyu.github.io/clusterProfiler/</guid>
      <description>The clusterProfiler package implements methods to analyze and visualize functional profiles of genomic coordinates (supported by ChIPseeker), gene and gene clusters.
clusterProfiler is released within the Bioconductor project and the source code is hosted on  GitHub.
 Author Guangchuang Yu, School of Public Health, The University of Hong Kong.
  Citation Please cite the following article when using clusterProfiler:
    Yu G, Wang L, Han Y and He Q*.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Documentation</title>
      <link>https://guangchuangyu.github.io/clusterProfiler/documentation/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Jul 2016 16:30:13 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://guangchuangyu.github.io/clusterProfiler/documentation/</guid>
      <description>Vignettes  DOSE: Disease enrichment analysis DOSE: Disease GSEA Statistical analysis and visualization of functional profiles for genes and gene clusters    Blog posts  News and updates  clusterProfiler in Bioconductor 2.8 clusterProfiler: an R Package for Comparing Biological Themes Among Gene Clusters BioC 3.1: NEWS of my BioC packages BioC 3.2: NEWS of my BioC packages BioC 3.3: NEWS of my BioC packages BioC 3.4: NEWS of my BioC packages    ID conversion  convert biological ID with KEGG API using clusterProfiler    Enrichment analysis  GO analysis using clusterProfiler use simplify to remove redundancy of enriched GO terms KEGG Module Enrichment Analysis KEGG enrichment analysis with latest online data using clusterProfiler DAVID functional analysis with clusterProfiler functional enrichment for GTEx paper use clusterProfiler as an universal enrichment analysis tool functional enrichment analysis with NGS data leading edge analysis a formula interface for GeneOntology analysis  bioinfoblog.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Featured Articles</title>
      <link>https://guangchuangyu.github.io/clusterProfiler/featured-articles/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Jul 2017 21:08:13 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://guangchuangyu.github.io/clusterProfiler/featured-articles/</guid>
      <description>Let us know if you have published using clusterProfiler and your publication will be featured here.
 2018 High-resolution spatiotemporal transcriptome mapping of tomato fruit development and ripening. Nature Communications. 2018, 364.
The prolyl isomerase FKBP25 regulates microtubule polymerization impacting cell cycle progression and genomic stability. Nucleic Acids Research. 2018
Microbiome Influences Prenatal and Adult Microglia in a Sex-Specific Manner. Cell. 2018.
Gene co-expression analysis for functional classification and gene–disease predictions.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>